{
  "Questions": {
    "1": {
      "question": "What is the name of the red-nosed reindeer?",
      "answer1": "Comet",
      "answer2": "Dasher",
      "answer3": "Blitzen",
      "answer4": "Rudolph",
      "correctAnswer": 4
    },
    "2": {
      "question": "In which country did the tradition of putting up a Christmas tree originate?",
      "answer1": "France",
      "answer2": "Germany",
      "answer3": "Norway",
      "answer4": "Sweden",
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    "3": {
      "question": "What popular Christmas beverage is also called \"milk punch\"?",
      "answer1": "Eggnog",
      "answer2": "Hot chocolate",
      "answer3": "Apple cider",
      "answer4": "Mulled wine",
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    "4": {
      "question": "Which Christmas carol contains the lyric \"Fa la la la la, la la la la\"?",
      "answer1": "Silent Night",
      "answer2": "Jingle Bells",
      "answer3": "Deck the Halls",
      "answer4": "O Holy Night",
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    "5": {
      "question": "What is the name of the main villain in \"The Nightmare Before Christmas\"?",
      "answer1": "Oogie Boogie",
      "answer2": "Jack Skellington",
      "answer3": "Sandy Claws",
      "answer4": "Zero",
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    "6": {
      "question": "Which country is the largest exporter of Christmas trees?",
      "answer1": "United States",
      "answer2": "Canada",
      "answer3": "Norway",
      "answer4": "Denmark",
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    "7": {
      "question": "What figure from English folklore came to be associated with Santa Claus?",
      "answer1": "Father Christmas",
      "answer2": "Robin Hood",
      "answer3": "The Green Man",
      "answer4": "Jack Frost",
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    "8": {
      "question": "What is the real name of the character Tim Allen plays in \"The Santa Clause\"?",
      "answer1": "Scott Calvin",
      "answer2": "Nick Claus",
      "answer3": "Chris Kringle",
      "answer4": "Jack Frost",
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    "9": {
      "question": "What is the name of the fruitcake traditionally served in Italy at Christmas?",
      "answer1": "Pandoro",
      "answer2": "Panettone",
      "answer3": "Tiramisu",
      "answer4": "Cassata",
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    "10": {
      "question": "What is the name of the first artificial Christmas tree made from?",
      "answer1": "Feathers",
      "answer2": "Metal",
      "answer3": "Plastic",
      "answer4": "Bristles",
      "correctAnswer": 1
    }
  }
}
